Your husband and I are not
in a relationship.
I hope you can forgive me.
Sorry if I doubted you.
I'm also at fault.
Does this mean that our family
is okay again?
Are we whole again?
We are not broken.
Here in my heart,
our family is whole.
My contact said that Golda
has already given a statement.
Matias, you know the drill.
Joey is texting.
Emergency?
We need volunteers
for the games.
Hey, why are you here?
Are you a stalker?
This is my sister's foundation.
What are you guys doing here?
We are participating
in the games.
Welcome to our foundation's
annual "Palarong Puso"!
Let the games begin!
That's how you want to play?
- It was an accident.
- Okay, go.
You think I don't know?
You two are doing it
intentionally.
I didn't mean it.
If it was intentional.
I would've done this.
You cannot do that, Jin Ho.
Can you just stop fighting?
You're on your own.
Now I get it.
I understand why you like Joey
so much.
They like you.
Hey, that's impossible.
I'm pretty to the max.
That's true.
Our next game is the longest
line!
So on the count of three...
One, two, three, go!
Hey, stop that, stop that.
That's not allowed.
Hey, that's not allowed.
Go inside. Get dressed.
Andrew, come on. Get dressed.
Oh, my God.
Get dressed, get dressed.
Oh, come on, hurry up!
Hurry up! Get dressed!
- My God!
- We won.
Wait a minute.
It's a tie between Team Andrew,
Peter, and...
Hey here.
Cool down first so you don't
undress there.
Come on, it's heavy.
Thank you.
Sorry.
We promised them
that we would do our best.
We too, fight if we fight.
Right, Jin Ho?
For sure!
That's how it should be
and not be sore losers
and take off your clothes.
It's embarrassing for the kids.
You're driving us crazy.
Joey, I have a question.
So among the three of us,
who's the best body?
I was just looking at the game,
not at you. You smell.
Okay, okay.
You want us to show again?
Oh, no! I don't want to see.
Yuck. Stop right there.
You know, the next game
is about to start.
Hurry up there.
You smell! Don't be like that.
Hey, let's go, quick.
I think she's just shy because
she thinks I have the best body.
- Show. Show it.
- Here, here.
Is that what you two
are showing?
That's nothing compared to this.
That's not impressive either.
Go home now.
You're arrogant. Let's go.
Grumpy.
Did everyone enjoy it?
You know, we enjoyed it too,
because they're really good,
especially in the Pie Eating
Contest!
My favorite, Friend,
was the relay.
Didn't they do well in that?
Yes. That means,
you all are great!
And as early as now,
I congratulate you all
because you did your best.
And for me, you are all winners!
But of course, this is it.
You are the top 4 teams,
as I said earlier,
who will meet to play tug
of war.
So it's like this: Two teams
will fight, right?
Yes, and whoever wins
against you,
they will be the ones
to face off in the final round.
- There.
- Yes!
So now, we'll call out
the names.
Okay, let's go with the ladies
first. Joey and Mary.
Of course, Peter and Lito, too.
Yes, come here too,
Jin Ho and Nono.
Yes!
And Andrew and Jeff.
That's it!
So, I have a question.
Yes?
Whose team will go together?
That's a very good question.
But of course, since they are
the only girls in this game,
they will pick the,
you know, yeah,
the team that they will partner
with, okay?
- Okay, that's it?
- Okay. Do you understand?
- Understand!
- Perfect. Go!
- Team Andrew!
- Yes!
We can handle those!
Stay focused! Fighting!
- Are you ready?
- Of course!
- Ready!
Okay, game!
Because you are ready,
on the count of three...
One, two, three, pull!
- Did you eat?
- Let's go! Pull!
One, two, pull!
We won!
- Let's go!
- We have a winner!
Congratulations, guys!
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry too.
Are you okay?
Oh no, come on.
What happened?
You're bleeding.
Come on, rest for now, Mary.
Thank you.
I told you not to hurt anyone,
didn't I?
You know, because you were
such an attention seeker,
and you were so competitive,
the kid got hurt.
I'm sorry, Joey,
we didn't mean to.
You know, I brought you here
because I wanted to thank you.
Do you know this is
a children's game?
But it seems like you're
the childish ones.
You know, this happened,
it's all part of the game.
It's not part of the game
when you throw eggs.
Childish.
Just stay here, driver,
and someone will help me.
I'll help you too,
so we can be quick.
There.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
Be careful.
How do I...
We need to her that before
she goes inside.
Mother.
Hey, Joey.
- Help! Please help.
- Let me help you.
I thought...
You're still busy inside,
that's why you're not answering.
Earlier, you were a bit busy,
but the game is over.
Let me help you.
Just a moment, Joey.
Are you okay?
When you're lucky, the mother
and daughter are together.
I'm okay.
Why do you look like that?
Your face looks long.
No, no, Mother.
It's obvious, Joey.
What is it?
Maybe Delgado will get
the message.
He'll just shut up
and keep quiet in jail.
Won't he even go crazier, Boss?
Let him go crazy...
if he wants to never see
his family again.
Let's work out a strategy
for this.
Jin Ho and Peter
are so competitive,
to the point that a kid got hurt
because of them.
Oh my, what happened to the kid?
She just got a scratch,
but she's been treated.
Those two are just really
annoying.
Joey, you're a bit OA too.
I wondered what happened
to the kid.
It turned out it was just
a scratch.
Luckily, she's okay.
My goal today is for you
to enjoy to the fullest.
Oh, come on.
Mother, let me. I'll help you.
There, someone will help.
That's right.
Two guys have arrived, Boss.
Those guys don't stand a chance
with us.
If they fight back,
we'll knock them down.
Help, please.
You guys are so big.
Joey, we're really sorry.
You're sorry.
We ruined your day.
Peace.
Let's go.
Why, Boss?
I thought we could handle those?
Stupid!
The other guy is Berdugo's
brother-in-law.
He can't see me.
You can give him.
- It's okay.
- You can handle that.
What's that?
Let's go.
- Hey!
- Oh my...
- Who's there?
- Jin Ho.
- Don't follow...
- Give me that.
Let's go.
Hey, come back here!
You don't know who that is!
They are gone.
The other one is crazy.
I saw the other one has a gun.
Both of them have guns.
Did anyone see their faces?
Not me.
Maybe you can use your
intelligence powers
to figure out who they are.
There was no plate on the car.
I can't make a trace on them.
What are they planning?
Joey and Ms. Clarissa...
- Let's go, let's go.
I've already reported
the two-armed men.
They said they'll be doing
the rounds
because there might be someone
else lurking around.
Well, for sure,
they won't come back.
Maybe they're scared of these
troublemakers.
But in fairness,
even if these three are
troublemakers,
they are strong and alert.
They protected me and my mother.
So, thank you.
Well, you guys have probably
saved the day.
But you shouldn't have chased
them anymore.
You saw them with guns.
Maybe those are just carjackers?
Maybe.
That's why they're the ones
in the car.
But why did they bring out
their guns right away
if the car is what they're
after?
Could it be that my daughter
and I are their targets?
Maybe...
maybe this is related to...
My husband's case.
Oh my god, Clarissa.
What if you're right?
Maybe you need security.
Ma'am, we'll just request
it from Chief Lansang.
Maybe, Mother,
the one who framed Father
is really scared too.
Because Father's case
is very strong.
And I'm sure that when Father
is acquitted,
he'll find a way to expose
that syndicate.
When that happens,
our lives will be back
to normal.
We won't be afraid and hide
anymore, right, Mother?
Well, you really inherited
that from your father, Joey.
Always positive thinking.
That's why I'm only holding on
to you now.
Of course, Mother.
Never say die?
- Never say die.
They wanted to join.
You guys got involved.
I was going to have a surprise
for you, Berdugo.
I thought I'd get Delgado's
family.
I was going to scare him
so that the policeman
who's a thorn in our throats
would shut up, but I failed.
Why?
Your brother-in-law came.
He even chased us.
Son of a...
Did they see you?
No, Berdugo.
It was dark.
They didn't catch us.
This problem with Delgado
has been going on for too long.
We need to bring out
all the aces.
For our 4th place,
the winner is the team of...
That's Team Joey!
There!
- Congratulations!
- Yes!
Next up, our 3rd place,
is the team of...
Andrew! Team, Andrew!
The 2nd place is the team of...
- Yes, Team Peter!
- Peter!
- Congratulations!
- Congrats!
That means, our champion
is the team of...
Team Jin Ho!
Congratulations, winners!
Congratulations, everyone!
Yes!
Congrats!
Idol!
Okay, let's take photos.
Photo op now.
Let's come here.
Let's all take a picture.
In fairness, that suits you.
You guys are like heroes.
Well, you are our heroes,
both for Mother and me.
You know, I admit it.
I know I want to win because you
used to be impressed with me.
But now, you seem to be more
impressed with these two.
Oh, no.
I'm impressed with you.
Besides, our friendship
is deeper,
so don't be insecure.
I have to admit.
It's kind of weird for me.
I'm not used to having friends.
I'm more used to competing,
always giving my best or else...
there will be consequences.
You know, friendship shouldn't
be forced.
Besides,
there shouldn't be any
punishment when you can't do it.
And you don't have to prove
anything to me
because you're already
my friend.
As for me, I'm just happy
because we're allies today.
because I'm not used to being on
the same side.
In fairness, you're okay being
on the same side.
Besides, you seem happier
when I'm by your side,
I mean, the three of us.
You know, it's hard to find true
friends these days,
so we should value each other,
not fight.
So we should take care
of our friendship, right?
What? Solid?
Never say die.
Solid.
Game.
You know, let's take a picture
the four of us.
The four of us?
Mister, please take a picture.
Sorry, sorry to you.
Thank you.
You're in the middle now.
Yes! Congrats, Boy!
Hey my ears,
your voice is so loud.
Jin Ho!
Wait!
Joey?
- Yeah.
- Is there a problem?
No, no. I just want to give you
something.
I just wanted to give
that to you
so that no matter where you go,
you'll never forget that you
have friends, that you have us.
Thank you.
Just be careful,
and don't miss us.
Don't miss me.
Bye! Be careful!
Okay, bye.
- Jin Ho!
- Go!
- Joey, come on!
- Get out of here!
Let's go ahead!
Let's leave them!
- Jin Ho!
- Oppa!
We are worried about you!
I'm okay.
You're bleeding.
It's nothing.
No, let's go to the hospital.
You have to get checked.
No, I'm really okay.
Don't worry.
- Shot!
- Shot?
Make it good.
Joey! Come on. Go, Joey.
Theresa...
It's not just about you and me.
I have to protect my friends.
No...
I have to protect Joey.
Judge, can I disturb you
even though you are busy?
Matias, what do you need?
We need to talk.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is it okay?
Delicious!
Really?
Yes, look so domesticated,
you're cooking for Andrew.
What do you mean
by domesticated?
You're something else.
Because this is the only way
I can think of to thank him.
Well, why? Aren't you attracted
to him?
He's tall, handsome,
with almond eyes,
and smells good.
Aren't those kinds
of men your type?
I don't look at him.
So you should look at him.
You'll see.
You know, you're stubborn, too?
Yeah, right.
This must be okay.
This sinigang is delicious.
Oh, no, that's for Andrew.
That's embarrassing.
Isn't it?
Delicious.
Okay, I'll put that on.
It might not be enough for
Andrew.
Why is your face like that?
Is there a problem?
- There is.
- Attorney...
I'm sorry, Miss Delgado.
The court did not accept
the witness statement
due to technicalities.
What?
Guys, my vlogger friend texted.
But now, we need to go
to Bolagos Lake first.
They definitely won't find
anything on those bodies.
If this is traced back to me,
I'll throw you next.
When Berdugo catches me,
that's what I'll definitely
end up with.
Joey, I went home as soon
as I found out.
One of the bodies has been
identified
through dental records.
Is Godfather Diego one
of the bodies found?
I just remembered our employee
asking for help.
Clarissa?
I want to meet her as soon
as possible.